nakedpr.com 2011-06-30

# » Privacy Policy / Social Realist

## Privacy Policy

At SocialRealist.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use or visit SocialRealist.com, and how we safeguard your information. **We never sell or rent your personal information to third parties.**

**Log Files**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. This information is used privately by the site administrator to make improvements to the site. It is also used to identify spammers and trolls when necessary. While this information may be used to expose those spammers and trolls the IP address and related details will not be shared with anyone else other than if required by a court of law.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site.

We also use third party advertisements on SocialRealist.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geo-targeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

_This Privacy Policy Template Provided by[JenSense](http://www.jensense.com/) and edited for use on this site._
